[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ area of Frankfurt is to the south east of the city center.", "Opt_1": "commercial", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "to do with business", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lack of financial aid is a significant ____ on the chances of success in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "margin", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As the advisor, you often have other responsibilities that do not always permit giving undivided ____ to the organization.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The third stage of the writing process is when you ____ your work. This means that you make any necessary changes to its structure or content.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "multiply", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to increase greatly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Never has the ____ of a stable, prosperous, and democratic hemisphere seemed so close within reach.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has made ____ good progress this year, but I still think she could have done better if she had tried harder.", "Opt_1": "occasionally", "Opt_2": "fairly", "Opt_3": "indirectly", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_2_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_3_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school tried to ____ the fact that one of its teachers had a criminal record.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written ____ within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a legitimate reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "tool", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "something used to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is fair to ____ the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment among older people.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers did not ____ because of students behaving badly but rather because student behavior was not adequately managed.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "migrate", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You must enter the US using the visa document issued by the ____ you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users ____ from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to finance their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Here is a good opportunity to get paid for conducting undergraduate research at UH through its Summer ____ Program.", "Opt_1": "Shortage", "Opt_2": "Research", "Opt_3": "Directions", "Opt_4": "Display", "Answer": "Research", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to ____ global warming. Many people say that the whole affair was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "discuss", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The business tried to ____ its employees to work harder by offering an extra day's holiday to the best salesperson.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your work is ____ but I'm sure you could do better if you tried harder.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "satisfactory", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Antarctica is a very ____ environment. Many explorers have lost their lives there.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Terrorists ____ large areas of the country outside of the main towns.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students choosing this option must select a faculty adviser from the departmental faculty who will ____ the student's program.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "supervise", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is easy to ____ the government for its failures, but no-one has come up with any better ideas.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A doctor will usually ask her patient many questions in order to make a ____ of the illness.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "adhere", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher said that he could not ____ to grade all the papers by the next lesson.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She found that the document had no ____ and conflicted with the assessments of military intelligence.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "detail", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We dedicate all our efforts and resources to the ____ and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "To separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Until you are an adult you do not have the ____ to do what you want.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has set the ambitious ____ of halving child poverty by the year 2020.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "motive", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "reason", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you want to make an ____ measurement of the weight of very small objects, you will need a special electronic balance.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "scarce", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "rare, not abundant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is the completely ____ response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "rational", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The construction of new facilities is an ____ for any university to make a clear statement about its environmental concern.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Compliment employees in public but always ____ them in private; this shows your respect for them and avoids embarrassment.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but ____ statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students must ____ a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical passage into English.", "Opt_1": "range", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Computer viruses ____ themselves to documents such as word processing files and spreadsheets.", "Opt_1": "appear", "Opt_2": "remain", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "undergo", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to receive or experience"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It offers an ____ solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills minor as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to ____ and investigate the extent of the problem.", "Opt_1": "append", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The decision to make cannabis ____ in small amounts is a significant shift in the government's policy.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The management is considering removing the salesmen's ____ to use company cars at the weekend for private purposes.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Given the abundance of oxygen and silicon in the crust, it should not be surprising that the most ____ minerals in the earth's crust are the silicates.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was only one stage in a long struggle that did not come to a ____ end until 1971.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "trigger", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was highly confidential and did not ____ his (personal) accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Her problems began to ____ themselves after she was absent for more than a month.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "manifest", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are ____ for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not owe Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "equivalent", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "equal to; the same as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "label", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is a common belief that the universe is infinite. But who knows? Maybe one day we will ____ it has an edge or end.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "announce", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For this task, instructors present a ____ of steps in a mixed order and students are asked to re-order the items into the correct sequence.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It must be obvious what the primary theme of each section is, and how that theme connects with the paper's ____ theme.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I usually keep a ____ of spare pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "equipment", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "suppress", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would resist and ____ that heritage.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government should ____ all its energy to reducing unemployment.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you submit your application in person, there will be a ____ of up to 48 hours following receipt of your application before you can enroll for classes.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When a student comes to a lesson having learned a poor habit, time and money are lost and ____ is postponed.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When the earth is closest to the sun, the ____ between the earth and sun is 147000000k.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This ____ is more evident in those sciences in which the technological requirements have increased to a significant extent.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Take 3 grams of sodium chloride and an ____ amount of sugar.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "ESL students fare better in classrooms where the teacher is ____ of their special needs.", "Opt_1": "aware", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "knowing", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military ____ in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "enhance", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to make something better", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to modify tried-and-tested methods and habits ____ than allocate more resources.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "rather", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You must write a ____ of 3 pages for your final report.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not ____ one another.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "contradict", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My ____ impression of him is that he is very intelligent and that his poor behaviour is because of boredom.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "preliminary", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ will investigate the process by which the decision was made.", "Opt_1": "committee", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "aim", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lincoln's early position as president was that slavery could remain in current slave states but could not ____ to new states or territories.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nazi paramilitary organization was compulsory, although he was never a ____ of the Nazi party and his family opposed Hitler's regime.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most schools do a lot to ____ their students of the dangers of smoking.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "overlap", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "One factor was political: because we had decided to ____ the project at first to the six northernmost counties in our region.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "compete", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How do I request that the Libraries ____ a book or other material?", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "deliver", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In my opinion you are being too ____ if you think you can learn a language in less than a year.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has no ____ to tell people how to live.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The book focuses on the key role the family plays as teenagers navigate the difficult ____ from childhood to adulthood.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "On the rare ____ when Crockett looks upon Indians with anything less than pure hatred, his observations continue to feed upon common stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ why he made such a foolish decision.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He had no good reason for being late, so he decided to ____ one.", "Opt_1": "analyze", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not ____ it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to extend a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "abnormal", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school plans to illuminate the sports ____ so that games can be played after dark.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You must turn in the ____ by next Friday. There can be no delay.", "Opt_1": "topic", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your ____ task for this lesson is to work together to prepare a presentation on air pollution.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The meeting ended very late but the administration still did not have time to ____ all the issues it wanted to.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote among northerners, did not ____ a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the immediate future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of ____ reform strategies.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "education", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "schooling", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government of Israel again stated that the attack was not ____ and that it would be investigated.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "deliberate", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was a chance to try out something different and immerse myself completely in another culture and it was a ____ I did not regret.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She finally was able to ____ her true ability with an excellent score in the end of year test.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "He is the ____ choice for the leading role in the play. He's by far the best actor in the school.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I was unable to ____ the reason for Angelica's sudden departure at the beginning of the second trimester.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have a ____ chance of passing your exams if you work really hard for the rest of the term.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "forthcoming", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "coming soon", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "attract", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a minor consideration in the ____ decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On hearing of the terrorist ____ the president called an immediate meeting of his top advisers.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "exponent", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we assume that the ____ of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students are responsible for gathering all ____ necessary to support an appeal.", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Assad did not want to ____ a cease-fire until Israel evacuated at least those parts of the Golan Heights occupied in the October war.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane ____ of slaves but did not condemn the practice.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At this ____ of our research we were unable to find a means for accessing the actual decisions made in these cases.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "stage", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "period of time, part of a process"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has announced ____ plans to reduce long-term unemployment.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't ____ career counseling.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to publish if the ____ of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You should follow the ____ that the doctor has given you.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "territory", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "land; area (of interest)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to ____ on, critically analyze, and evaluate their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to ____ employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with regard to top performers.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He has a strong ____ against religion since suffering badly as a child in a strictly religious school.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although two weeks are dedicated to its development at the end of the semester you should not conclude that this is enough time for the ____ project.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her poor behaviour, but promised never to repeat it.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase ____ tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Bush administration has failed to ____ the matter urgently, spending only \ufffd\ufffd1.3 billion per year.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right mixture of ____ that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students must ____ a working knowledge of a foreign language by translating a mathematical passage into English.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher look like she was going to ____ angrily when I came late, but fortunately for me, she didn't!", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "deny", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The settlers decided to ____ the settlement and sail back to Cuba.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "choice", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "decision, selection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "____ times for farming can also mean tough times for marriages.", "Opt_1": "Distinct", "Opt_2": "Flexible", "Opt_3": "Essential", "Opt_4": "Tough", "Answer": "Tough", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore he was unable to ____ that he was breaking new methodological ground.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "However, no one criterion will be the ____ reason for lack of admission to the program.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The new teacher ____ it difficult to control the class.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Internet businesses will only be successful if they use the ____ of clear, easy, cheap, safe shopping.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The town council has been criticized for not providing enough ____ for young people in the town.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an evident ____ that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "remedy", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company has decided to ____ its main attention to increasing business in the developing Chinese market.", "Opt_1": "retain", "Opt_2": "cover", "Opt_3": "devote", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "devote", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_3_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Politicians ____ that they can't know everything, so they surround themselves with people who can advise them.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "realize", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most older cultures seem to ____ volcanoes as a natural part of life and adjust their habits accordingly.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "provide", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to give", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This semester-long project begins with an overview in which students think about how to ask scientific questions and ____ hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In ____ to make student learning relevant to real life experiences, learning environments must be authentic.", "Opt_1": "order", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is still too soon to say whether the invasion of Iraq was ____ it.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You will ____ recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and suggest alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There was a ____ in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main focus of teaching.", "Opt_1": "forecast", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "prediction", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "coincidence", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To develop a comprehensive approach to business, managers must ____ the strengths of their employees in assigning tasks.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Audio software can help students to record their spoken words describing an abstract ____ or how to perform a computation.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ problem facing the world this century is how to reduce global warming.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Loo (= toilet) is not a word that you should use in ____ situations.", "Opt_1": "formal", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an ____ pattern that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Bible laid down some rules for the humane treatment of slaves but did not ____ the practice.", "Opt_1": "condemn", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a constant ____ at all heights.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All new systems to the data center will need to undergo a security scan or audit ____ to installation.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The New Investigator Competition is an award for the best paper by a graduate student, carrying with it a prize valued at ____ \ufffd\ufffd500.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot comply with this law ____ to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The agent's ____ for selling a house is usually a percentage of the sale price.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There's no incentive to make an ____ if the teacher never gives you back your work.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The college is aggressively working to ____ engineering education and develop leaders for the 21st century workforce.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "magnify", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best ____ to announce that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Progress is so fast these days that some technological products become ____ within a very short time.", "Opt_1": "obsolete", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "obsolete", "Opt_1_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government promised to ____ its policy on drug criminality.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and perpetual problem of dealing with our ____ waste?", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "balance", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "equalness", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will generate much debate in the classroom, mainly ____ graduate students.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Archaeologists found some Roman coins ____ the town wall.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of ____ to complete this class.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "materials", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Parents who ____ their children were often ____ed themselves.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you do not ____ to the rules of the school, you will be asked to leave.", "Opt_1": "halt", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "adhere", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ resulted in a statistic that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While the system has offered men the opportunity to become owners of small factories, this opportunity rests on the unpaid ____ of female family members.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The proposed system seems an improbable ____ for the short-term, given that a half century of work with this goal has met only limited success.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "terminate", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to finish or stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a ____ far greater than its economic substance.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because of the interactive nature of the classroom, absences will significantly affect your ____ in the course.", "Opt_1": "performance", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "cause", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the homework for me? I'm not sure I understand.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a ____ tool for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Coca Cola is a name that is ____ to most people in the world.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "familiar", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should ____ to the topic sentence.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "release", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A great ____ of discussion focused on observations which could solve the mystery by testing the predictions of the various hypotheses.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to contemplate the reasons for your ____ of success.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is inevitable that any complex ____ will have some sort of taxation system.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teachers need to regularly ____ the quality of their student's work.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school had similar exam results to last year, with the ____ion ____ that mathematics scores were a little higher.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main consequence of these wars is the social unrest, and the increasing ____ and social divergence between the groups of the community.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We explain that at each movement in the dance there are endless opportunities to ____ new ideas.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "cancel", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to cut or stop from happening"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Gandhi, who brought independence to India, was an ____ man.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ to save life has recently been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This ____ is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Remember that you ____ me \ufffd\ufffd20.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "accept", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not exhibit any ____ of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "conflict", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "reluctance", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "unwillingness; hesitation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the ____ to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Scientists have found life over a mile below the ____ of the sea, far from the sun.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If he was indeed employed by the Grand Duke, that would ____ for his odd behaviour.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and ____ invisible to ships.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The test will be a ____ of reading comprehension passages and short writing texts.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We must ____ the trend of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "dispose", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and ____ other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I want to ____ you that I shall be leaving the school at the end of the next term.", "Opt_1": "inform", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Her ____ skills are very good; she has much more difficulty with calculation.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Most students are ____ about the suggestion to replace the blackboards with whiteboards.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "principal", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to ____ its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The entire structure of Iraqi military and civil ____ collapsed so completely as the war ended, leaving a vast problem for American troops to handle.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "society", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_4_def": "win"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We could not detect any significant ____ of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and duration of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "instruction", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "attention", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "focus", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She found that the document had no detail and conflicted with the assessments of ____ intelligence.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The dropout ____ for high schoolers rose to 3.8 percent during the last decade.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A high percentage of students are not ____ of tutoring services offered by the College of Engineering.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no ____ without law, and no valid law or legal system when ____ is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "materials", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "liberty", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people ____ government elections every four years instead of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "advocate", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The North Viet Namese Army was not ____ enough to outflank southern forces.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The June 1992 Gender Equity Study found a significant ____ in salaries between men and women.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We recognize that ____ beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an ____ security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Your answer should include three ____ causes of the disaster.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The student was ____ active with the experiment and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the research questions involved are ____ to more mainstream systems research, albeit larger in scale.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "permanent", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no mechanism in the ____ plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "master", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students post messages and ____ ideas through the bulletin board.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "exchange", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug ____ underlie many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "defend", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have ____ problems than children in more stable placements.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "radical", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "extreme, strong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How people react to music is subjective. What ____s good to one person may ____ terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you plan for your child to attend the school, you must ____ an online request.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "dismiss", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "submit", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students have been invited to comment on the ____ of the school's new sports facility.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Different newspapers will often have a different ____ of the same event - especially newspapers from different parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Use this form when you need to ____ accidentally deleted files from the network.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "infer", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a ____ request for extension of the project due date.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The company had to amend their ____ predictions after the cost of oil doubled within 6 months.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "fee", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to the severe ____ of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to assemble a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Be sure to isolate and disinfect feeding ____ and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "survey", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This ____ provides a quick and extremely simple way to collect written feedback on student learning.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To find out more about a ____ event, click on the event name from the pop-up menu on the left or click on a link below.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If we accept your request to ____ the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the ____ment.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The best way to ____ that your machine has a unique name is to use your University account name for your computer name.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "criticize", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to develop ____ receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results represented an unusual ____ of old and modern practices.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "mixture", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "combination", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "explicit", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Unfortunately, the data was not ____ and often inaccurate.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "From my perspective as a teacher and parent, I would say that her difficulties in school are ____ to problems at home.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "severe", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "An ____ will occur if this software is not installed on the user's machine.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "belief", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some historians still ____ to label the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "AOL has said that this is a very dangerous virus and that there is NO ____ for it at this time.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "remedy", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "World War II was a turning ____ because, for the first time, women were allowed to join the military.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The State Department has seen a drastic ____ in passport applications being filed since a recent change in policy.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The book had arrived in ____s by Sunday evening but ____ managers were under strict instructions not to even open the boxes and put it on the shelves.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "achieve", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To ____ their high salary, top managers like to refer to the increased risk that they will lose their jobs.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "persuade", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "justify", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance rank is ____ of maternal rank, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest rank between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It offers an effective solution to a problem based on good audience analysis, and fulfills ____ as well as all major purposes.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He was expelled from school for a deliberate ____ to cheat in the end of year exams.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "attempt", "Answer": "attempt", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to try"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "However, it would be foolish to ____ that our planet has seen the last of this powerful and frightening virus.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This also helps you determine which variables it is essential to control to avoid an ____ answer.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "physical", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "of the body", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The requirements threaten to decrease family and individual student ____ over the transition process.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "That doesn't mean I have a personality disorder because I conduct myself in a different ____ to different people.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's too easy to ____ all of the country's problems on the government.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "confine", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This article will only ____ the issues rather than present a detailed analysis with proofs.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I was headed into new ____ not in what I was teaching but in how I was to teach it.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You must remember to ____ all the images and other HTML documents you have created and referenced in your \"Public/html\" directory.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Ours is the only ____ that can prevent a massive loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "status", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "position, standing", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations ____ the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Seminar is an intensive examination of ____ policy making in Washington.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He did not ____ the problem until too late.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We should never ____ or blame any person on account of outward actions that are common to all; but only on account of their principles.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If this request is approved by the IRB, the researcher and his or her clinic ____ would be permitted to review the medical records.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "target", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school wanted to ____ students from families outside the usual sphere of business and finance.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Today the World Bank, which is ____ responsible for the disaster of the last thirty years, acknowledges that the standards for human development are falling in Africa.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "incentive", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to ____ energy and help contribute to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "assert", "Opt_2": "consume", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "conserve", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to preserve; to not use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The patient was not at all happy with the standard of ____ she received while in hospital.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "grant", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "By the late 1960's it was ____ that another relocation of the laboratory was going to be necessary.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is evidence that increases in short sale transactions ____ stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students will undertake comprehensive analysis of several works and will compile a database of ____ literature.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "quality", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The course will ____ the knowledge base regarding the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The fact that she doesn't speak English did much to ____ the situation.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of weight change through pregnancy was similar across the 3 projects.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We must be ____ in how we interpret the data. It would be easy to draw false conclusions.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher said that he could not ____ to grade all the papers by the next lesson.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "feature", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most ____ reason for her poor test scores is that she didn't prepare herself well enough.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If authors ____ there is a significant error in a published paper, they may correct their paper by submitting a short correction notice.", "Opt_1": "realize", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the sole reason for the invasion of Iraq was to ____ control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most simply, the strength of a ____ is measured by determining how much energy is required to break the ____.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "device", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "object; method", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We often hear that now is the ____ of the most rapid change. From one perspective, this might be correct.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "diagram", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a type of picture or chart"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The university follows a ____ policy of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "vast", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to do well in tests then you will need to ____ the amount of time watching TV and spend more time studying.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "propensity", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the ____ words used and the explicit claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Let's make it clear from the beginning that there is no one thing that you can do to ____ everyone, or even to ____ the same person every time.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "observe", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to watch carefully"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm ____ was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "respectively", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "European governments strongly ____ the kidnapping of a German aid worker in Afghanistan.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in ____ and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ancient Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "society", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "society", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree that thought disorder and language disorder are ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ensure that the way we talk must not ____ any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "occupy", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Web sites such as Wikipedia certainly ____ the finding of information, although not all of it is reliable.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "facilitate", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to criticize the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "classic", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He said ____ times that money was not a factor in the decision, and it was not about safety alone.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to predict which infants in the latter group will not survive without support.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "rather", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "instead"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "furthermore", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "also, in addition"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "drastic", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "severe; great", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "spread", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You should not ____ that the test questions this semester will be on the same topics.", "Opt_1": "reduce", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "assume", "Opt_1_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They are never forgotten, those ____ moments of splendid victory sandwiched between so many slices of rancid defeat.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "profound", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "deep; great; serious"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "All new computer purchases by the University, and its various Auxiliaries, shall meet a ____ standard for both hardware and operating system.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many new astronomy learners, students and adults alike, are unfamiliar with the universe ____ the solar system.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If UVA is to ____ level of satisfaction among junior faculty, it must make an effort to align its policies and practices more closely with the needs and expectations of the faculty.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government report is set to ____ its report on nuclear energy tomorrow.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The additional time is necessary to enable him to make a ____ decision on an Alaska natural gas transportation system.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "sound", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An ____ of English that many learners find difficult is verb grammar.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In this class, we will examine the ____ about the risks generated by the war on terror.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the 20th century, if you wanted to kill lots of people, you needed a government ____ to do it.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "apparatus", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has taken the wise decision to ____ the public before passing the proposed law.", "Opt_1": "abuse", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not ____ our friendship in the least, I wished to avoid potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "monitor", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Homes were built and sold to families in need at no ____ and no interest.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to ____ on future developments, we need to consider the actual and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "coordinate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people think that the government's proposals to reduce teenage crime are ____ and will not work.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "superficial", "Answer": "superficial", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There has been no ____ statement about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "optional", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lebanese security officials said the soldiers' tank drove over a mine, but Israel said it could not ____ that.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After the attacks of September 11, 2001, Pat Cornell turned her ____ to detecting and preventing terrorism.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "supplementary", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The two procedures consistently showed that garlic did not inhibit the ____ of oral bacteria.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "innovation", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "new object or idea"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first ____ those principles and then consider the subsequent problems.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Stubbornness is a ____ that is sometimes positive and sometimes negative.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is too soon to ____ the success of the \"war on terror\".", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "frustrate", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nadeem has worked with FSU London since early 2004 as a permanent ____ of staff managing the Information Technology Systems.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "strategy", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the adult victim acknowledges having experienced abuse, it is important to ____ the potential for future violence, as well as the danger involved.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some parents do not appreciate how difficult it is to provide an ____ that will meet the needs of all students.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The manager has decided form a committee to ____ the recent increase in theft from the storeroom.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The need for an alternative ____ to teacher certification has become evident.", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "route", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government reports a slight ____ in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "persist", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Plagiarism is easy to ____ but often hard to define. This is partly because the legal rules differ sharply from the ethical ones.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "condemn", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of this study is to determine whether antioxidants (Vitamins C and E) reduce the frequency of serious illness.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "During ____ stages of a planning process, review and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not contradict one another.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "homogeneous", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's not easy to ____ yourself when you're not going out and actually preparing for an opponent.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "motivate", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students successfully completing a family history major should ____ a significant range of skills and abilities in research and critical thinking.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "interrupt", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "demonstrate", "Answer": "demonstrate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has decided to revise it proposals to increase income tax after ____ demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "They did not ____ an attack. They responded to an attack from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "anticipate", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to expect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you are ____ and flexible, enjoy solving tasks independently and are committed to achieving outstanding performance, then this is the job for you.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The current program review ____ is not very valuable because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "background", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "family experiences; circumstances"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "However, the video does not ____ much real information; it was also not very emotionally compelling.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "convey", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dr. Carpenter told the jury that Hinckley was unable to ____ reality from fiction.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "journey", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "a long trip to a different place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Little association is found between the amount of homework young students ____ and achievement.", "Opt_1": "vast", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Congress seems to have taken a cautious approach to regulating a technology that is reinventing the very ____ in which ideas are expressed.", "Opt_1": "amount", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The use of gender- ____ language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to pursue a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to ____ in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Having access to the laptop does seem to have substantially increased the ____ feeling of having adequate resources to do the job.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "broad", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to convince the reviewer that the problem is ____ investigation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first exhaust all possibilities for Federal and state financial ____ programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "attack", "Opt_3": "aid", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_3_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once you've chosen the course or courses you wish to take, you should ____ COM so that we can reserve a place for you.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "drain", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to take away; to get rid of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is impossible to revive any Yuan play in its original style because the music is lost and its social ____ has changed.", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is not an ____ test for ESL beginners. It is far too difficult.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "vague", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The teaching profession is usually not attractive to those who are still pupils themselves. This choice of ____ is normally made much later.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has no ____ to tell people how to live.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "obstacle", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "authority", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many people believe that the 'war on terror' will be a ____ war.", "Opt_1": "perpetual", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Food prices are ____ rising again after many months of no change.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The best ____ of your essay is the fact that it was very easy to follow your line of argument.", "Opt_1": "sphere", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ street demonstrations against its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "exclude", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "straightforward", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This review found that some guidelines and standards for reprocessing ____ laryngoscopes are incomplete, inadequate, and not consistent with one another.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "rigid", "Opt_3": "utter", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "rigid", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_3_def": "complete, total", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to ____ the cost of complying with new requirements regarding data recording.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You have one last opportunity to show that you can work hard and ____ properly. If you don't take it, you will be asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "criterion", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The machine did not work properly because the person installing it did not ____ the instructions.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "condemn", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to express strong disapproval"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's financial performance has been ____ affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "overly", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "too", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The radioactivity in the drugs works to destroy the tumor but usually does not ____ healthy organs.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "damage", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the sequence of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "influence", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The administrative staff will inform the student supervisor when a student has failed to ____ required documents and other information.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If a child consistently begs to stay home from school, has extreme fear of being away from a parent etc., there may be a cause for ____ about the child.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Take 3 grams of sodium chloride and an ____ amount of sugar.", "Opt_1": "annual", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "yearly", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a ____ decision, but ultimately I think it was the student life that had the greatest impact on my decision to come to Wheaton.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "preserve", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The only ____ of having computers in the classroom is that they are loud and make the room hot.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "instinct", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The result of such abuse was increased poverty in Russia and lost ____ in the fairness of governmental institutions.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "belief", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The problem for France was that the population did not ____ of responsible citizens which were necessary for the desired liberal system.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some students see no ____ for learning German - especially if they know they will only be in the country for a short time.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Before this century there was little ____ between them; indeed, they did not think of themselves as two distinct kinds of people.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "defect", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a ____ of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too brief discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "facilitate", "Opt_2": "assist", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_2_def": "to help", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will lessen your chances of success if you are ____ from school so often.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Being overweight is no longer simply a health problem - it is a ____ of a greater cultural shift that shows no sign of fading.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "symptom", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is trying to ____ a new way to open tin cans.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "deduce", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is an insult in some countries to reject an ____ of the local food.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The experiment resulted in a ____ that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "decision", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Board of Trustees met in April 2006 to discuss this report, and decided to ____ the construction of a 500 kW turbine.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In 2000, over seventy percent of India's population, and ____ three quarters of its poor, lived in rural areas.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This is the room where we store the science ____ ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The more alert you are to the key words used and the ____ claims made in ads, the more aware you will become of your own use of words and ideas.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "fortunate", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "lucky"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "assemble", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The good result in the election does not give the government ____ to do whatever it wants.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no point in turning on the computer. The ____ isn't working.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "observe", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main ____ to such Research & Development programs is the fact that the market size and the prices of the new products are unknown.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nugent claimed that how technology is organized is ____ not a rational decision but rather one based on individuals and history.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the Program is to train students to investigate significant problems in human physiology using modern technology.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "margin", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When morality comes up against profit, it is ____ profit that loses.", "Opt_1": "seldom", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "rare", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The University may terminate the Contract at any time by giving thirty (30) days written ____ to the Contract.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Although we have already received a number of excellent proposals for papers, it has been decided to ____ the deadline for submissions.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is set to ____ the parents' request to extend their child's vacation by two days.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is possible to find the ____ of an object by measuring the amount of water that it displaces.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Turkish law requires foreign scholars to obtain ____ permission to carry out research at institutions in Turkey.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The student was hardly active with the ____ and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we ____ less familiar territory, namely the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is vital that we find better and cheaper ways to ____ energy than by burning coal or oil.", "Opt_1": "create", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "deny", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not ____ the problem until too late.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This section is not an alternative to reading course materials or attending lectures, but rather an opportunity ____ topics in greater detail.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "found", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The supervisor perceived Pullard as an incompetent employee, but did not ____ that he might be a security problem.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We did not ____ our selections on an author's nationality, religion, politics, or field of study; nor on an author's race or gender.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "base", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "assume", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "ESS is for students who envision getting involved in the social ____ in any capacity: as volunteer consultants, board members, managers, or entrepreneurs.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the display case, please ____ at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "prove", "Opt_2": "inquire", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to ask", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India acquire cars.", "Opt_1": "demand", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Program is designed to ____ researchers whose ISBM-supported work appears in the academic literature.", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Lincoln, while receiving a majority vote ____ northerners, did not receive a majority of ALL the popular votes.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "While mastery of both written and spoken English is considered to be an ____ attribute, students with documented hearing, speech and other disabilities will be reasonably accommodated in accordance with law.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "So far scientists have been unable to ____ in their efforts to find a cure for cancer.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "But it is not a ____ for comprehensive food safety programs throughout the food distribution system.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "substitute", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Neither of the two strategies was ____ in terms of performance.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not clear to me how you can ____ make cannabis legal and expect the consumption of it to go down.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The goal is to produce world-class scholars with capabilities in research, teaching, and ____ within the broad area of Information and Decision Sciences.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "service", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Since you have not attended class for the last seven weeks, I ____ that you are not interested in graduating.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most students agree that teachers need ____ them on how much they have learned.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The workers participated in an ____ to see if they worked harder with music in the background.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "symptom", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are leaving this week for the Dominican Republic to ____ extensive nurse practitioner training.", "Opt_1": "purchase", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to buy", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the student contacts you before or after the experiment with a ____ excuse, you can cancel the appointment without penalty.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Being the best tennis player in grade 7 is not enough to ____ you for the ISST sports competition.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "elect", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new procedure should help to ____ the number of problems resulting from adjustment to semester length.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "reduce", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police ____ set up a committee whose task was to investigate the reasons for the shooting of the wrong man.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "location", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "place, where something or someone is"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ vocabulary as the single most important aspect of learning English.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "declare", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to state", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Those who could not transform, chose not to, or who were considered a threat to the ____ were imprisoned and eliminated.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The book is at its best when it delves energetically into some ____ event, and draws out its abstract meaning with reference to the grand themes.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "novel", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "new", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Rather than worrying about anthrax, this is the time of year to make sure that those at high risk for the flu ____ their vaccinations.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too ____ a method of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "authentic", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "That ____ data that is consistent, easy to manipulate, and repeatable.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is an excellent report. The research is ____ and the writing clear.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "thorough", "Opt_4": "concise", "Answer": "thorough", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_4_def": "short, not detailed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the adult victim acknowledges having experienced abuse, it is important to ____ the potential for future violence, as well as the danger involved.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is a highly subjective ____ of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dr. Potts announced that he planned to ____ a broadly based committee of representatives to study the Indian issue.", "Opt_1": "yield", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to produce", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Financial aid is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families ____ the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "asset", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "advantage", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The names of new products such as cars are not chosen at random. A large amount of research goes into choosing the most ____ name.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "prompt", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "quick; on or before time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The cost of establishing links will ____ as improvements are made to the underlying communication infrastructure.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is fair to ____ the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment among older people.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "manufacture", "Opt_4": "praise", "Answer": "praise", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_4_def": "to express approval about something someone has done"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Court did not find it necessary to hear the testimony of the two forensic experts and did not ____ the possibility of ordering a further investigation.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The illegal downloading of music via the internet is widespread ____ young people.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ German family has 1.8 children.", "Opt_1": "average", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home ____ her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why have these countries failed to ____ despite receiving billions of dollars in assistance?", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "evaluate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The main ____ of her poor grades are her frequent absences from school.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "cause", "Opt_4": "area", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_4_def": "field, sphere"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The method of evaluation used will be determined by the instructor but will generally include a combination (or all) of the following: homework, quizzes, exams, and a ____ final exam.", "Opt_1": "comprehensive", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "full, complete", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The scientists that ____ the committee all work in the field of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There was also no apparent record of an attempt to measure the ____ between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "journey", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There was ____ applause from the audience when the speaker mentioned Mandela's name.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In a world of ____ problems but finite resources, competition for adequate attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want an ____ answer to almost any question you could ask, then Google will probably give it to you.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Advertising marketed directly to the consumer may minimize the risks and ____ the benefits of medications.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "revive", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the common ____ of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The problems of drug-taking at the school ____ to get out of control.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "threaten", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The nine women here say the ____ treatment of domestic workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The idea was to remove the possibility of a ____ court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "local", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "in the area where you live or work"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its tax proposals. They are less than clear to most people.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You may have learned the steps of the scientific method but, in your preparation, failed to ____ each step with an example.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many arguments would not ____ if people would define the words they use.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The company's intention was to ____ sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "So if they go extinct on one tropical mountain there is only a ____ chance that they will recolonize from a similar nearby mountain.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Well done. The result of all your ____ is an fine grade in your ESL test.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Looking up all the key words in an important ____ should be considered a background check for all literary analysis.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that function to a person who lacked the ____ to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "objective", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Today we will practise for the ____ test.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "forthcoming", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I will ____ my presentation with an example of sea pollution.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of ____ like a camera, it helps to have a diagram to look at.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Much of the literature reviewed by the committee failed to specify in sufficient ____ the definition of a medication error used in the study.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If she told you she gave you her work, you can ____ her. She is very honest and reliable.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When Penn State decided not to cancel classes, it seemed like a safe and ____ decision.", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ethnographic reports were clear and did not ____ conflicting information.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "From then on, the government tried to ____ the communists of being enemies of the fatherland.", "Opt_1": "eliminate", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To accommodate the great ____ shift now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "resident", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a person who lives in a place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the manner that best fits local ____ and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to ____ the world's languages into one comprehensive genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors ____ the difficulty of giving up smoking. That's why they recommend never starting.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The best advice I can give is to ____ advice. Life is too short to be distracted by the opinions of others.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "My teacher will not let me sit near to John any more. She says he is a bad ____ on me.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I would like to know the ____ of what happened in the computer lab at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Even today some Russian people refuse to ____ Stalin with the terrible crimes that were committed when he was Russian leader.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dhawan says that he is confident that the summer ____ cuts will prevent the economy from spiraling into a recession.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As a teacher educator, I believe that new teachers need to reflect on, critically analyze, and ____ their own teaching.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "item", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "thing, element", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The assessment was not independent of influence by Coca-Cola (i.e. the ____ report appeared to have been edited by Coca-Cola prior to its release.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "forthcoming", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "coming soon", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ in the cafeteria after lunch.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "highlight", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A verbal ____ is impossible to prove, and the organization will always maintain that it was a misunderstanding.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "contract", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "a written agreement, binding in law"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Monroe is a well-known ____ of the mechanical theory of education, with its cult of standardization, intelligence tests, etc.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "exponent", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In ____ to make student learning relevant to real life experiences, learning environments must be authentic.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "accuse", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to blame", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Once Grace Albee arrived in New York City in 1933, she was able to ____ herself to full-time printmaking and her art began to command serious national attention.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some solutions exist to improve the performance of these devices, but ____ there are limitations how accessible they can be made.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "sum", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was ____ of him to criticize the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "intense", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The population of a country will ____ if more people die than are born.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One of the great problems in social dynamics is that the dynamic systems are not ____ and are frequently subject to unpredictable change.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Transportation is not an important ____ in the marketing cost of the new product.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The students decided to ____ in their attempt to fight bullying in the school.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The purpose of this study is to investigate the ____ that men are better in mathematics than women.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to illustrate how the ____ works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "element", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Corms have shapes ____ to bulbs, but do not contain fleshy scales.", "Opt_1": "similar", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There are ____ reasons for his academic success. The most important one is his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you are a ____ of the school orchestra should have lunch early and come to the practice at 12.30.", "Opt_1": "member", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If we ____ just a little more, we will see that random is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "reflect", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "resign", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "propose", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging ____ for the employers to determine the factors that stimulate job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Be sure to ____ and disinfect feeding equipment and other objects that may have come in contact with the sick animals.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The whole new industry of purchasing drugs \"on line\" is another ____ where care and common sense are essential.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to ____ it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In my ____ the government's argument for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously affect your ____ grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This ____ text contains the typical method of trisecting a segment.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Through appointments and ____ the President was able to drain the Constitution of much of its meaning, with no public reaction.", "Opt_1": "area", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "phase", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors advise people to ____ the number of eggs they eat to 2-3 per week.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to analyze its ____ methods.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "apparatus", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This famous victory will ____ her place in the history of sport.", "Opt_1": "procure", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Curiously ____ from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The district of most big cities around the main ____ station is often a dangerous place to be at night.", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "train", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Military power is not an ____ tool to transform the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The school gave a ____ warning to the teacher who had arrived late to school several times that month.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "bold", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "brave", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you accept a housing ____ in the Summer Allocation and subsequently cancel it or fail to move in, you are charged an administrative fee.", "Opt_1": "debt", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In our ____ class on binary counting, we found a way to represent numbers using just two digits, 0 and 1.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some politicians ____ that too much immigration will result in fewer jobs for the people born in the country.", "Opt_1": "interrupt", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The new government has not yet proved itself ____ of making the right decisions in its foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The cost will not ____ anyone from participating in the program.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In order to make up a missed exam, you must produce written evidence within 48 hours of the exam which shows that you had a ____ reason to do so.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is a particular ____ to welcome several San Francisco State University alumni who embody all that we commemorate today.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "privilege", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Your reading is improving fast, but you should not ____ your writing. It is through writing that you show your teachers what you know or have understood.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "continue", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is no point in turning on the computer. The ____ isn't working.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "monitor", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We ____ all our efforts and resources to the education and preparation of all students.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "dedicate", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ it proposals to increase income tax after massive demonstrations on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "revise", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A good way to guess the meaning of a new word is to examine its ____ in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The report was designed to measure computer and Internet use ____ people with disabilities.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An international school is a place that cannot survive if there is ____ that certain groups of students are better than others.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "prejudice", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government would like to reform the health service but the doctors are ____ their proposals.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A snowstorm failed to ____ soccer practice on the Inlet early last week.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "request", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "opportunity", "Opt_3": "priority", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "chance", "Opt_3_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A rich parent has donated money to the school to ____ the building of a new sports block.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Of the questions asked in this ____ of the survey, having an explicit privacy policy is one of the highest percentage of responses.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China is, indeed, going through a ____, but it is not a ____ from capitalism to communism.", "Opt_1": "source", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The publishing company brought a ____ of its books to display to teachers.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "expense", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "cost", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not ____ a police order to halt and was shot.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Illegal drugs are grouped into one or other ____ according to how dangerous they are considered.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "series", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a number of things, one after the other"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We cannot allow a few disaffected children to continually interrupt the education of the ____ of the class.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the data in the same order for every questionnaire.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Could you please ____ this book to its proper place on the shelf.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "classify", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "overall", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "general", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The online instructor must incorporate the best practices of traditional teaching without the ____ of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When traveling off-road, the car sensors must be able to detect negative obstacles such as holes and ditches as well as ____ ones such as trees or other cars.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The use of gender- neutral language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the ____ use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some doctors have suggested that their training should be less theoretical and of more ____ use.", "Opt_1": "practical", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "abundant", "Answer": "practical", "Opt_1_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "existing in large quantities"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ financial aid to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "block", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "train", "Opt_4": "recommend", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's good to see students of different nationalities ____ so naturally as they do at our school.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "interact", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In 2000, over seventy percent of India's population, and ____ three quarters of its poor, lived in rural areas.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "roughly", "Answer": "roughly", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "about, approximately"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children who are moved more frequently are more likely to have subsequent problems than children in more ____ placements.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "rational", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "stable", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He had to ____ the fact that teaching was not the right job for him.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Historically, there was ____ for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and lack of funds for ____ programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is unlikely to rise above the ____ of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "News digest covers critical ____ health issues from around the world.", "Opt_1": "public", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "public", "Opt_1_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some animals, such as the tortoise or snail, have an ____ shell rather than an internal skeleton.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Difficult financial times must not force us to ____ the integration of teaching and research.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Advances in technology have increased the ____ of life and the ____ of change.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "victory", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "win"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An unexpected ____ was that there was also significant improvement in composition as well as in math for these students during the academic year.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "outcome", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A significant ____ of winning the bid for the next Olympic Games is that it will cost the country an enormous amount of money.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "drawback", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It takes a lot of training to ____ the skills in professions such as car mechanics or cooking.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "master", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Despite all the money spend on cancer research there is little ____ of a cure being found in the near future.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "incident", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "happening; event", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion ____ the East India Company in 1857, and the firm eventually was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher thought about the best opportunity to ____ that she was leaving to have a baby.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "announce", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Education has reduced the ____ at which the disease has spread throughout the population.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "rate", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If your students are not at the ____ you have planned for them in the middle of the quarter, you will need to investigate why this is so.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "level", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Do you ____ a valid, current driver's licence?", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "enhance", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to make something better", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Regional Oral History Office has moved to a ____ location.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Remember that more than one factor may be the cause of a problem and that symptoms may often ____ in their appearance.", "Opt_1": "overlap", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "overlap", "Opt_1_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Participants donate a small amount of blood or saliva, which will be used as a ____ to blood from children with genetic diseases.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "comparison", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "announce", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The only disappointing part of the book is a portion of the third chapter, which is devoted to an interesting but much too ____ discussion of FDR's foreign policy.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the ____ of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the homework for me? I'm not sure I understand.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "abundant", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning ____ to examine the interior of the human body.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government's election defeat is a ____ case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The current program review ____ is not very valuable because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Advances in technology have increased the ____ of life and the ____ of change.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Blair will need to ____ the Americans that Europeans will no longer permit Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We explain that at each movement in the dance there are endless opportunities to ____ new ideas.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ and multidisciplinary International Lincoln Center for American Studies offers a year-round cycle of events to students and the community.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some of the key personal resources that you will draw from include your ____ academic background, teaching style, life experience, and technical experience.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The cold, hard truth is that your parents' ____ was more open to experimentation, social change and an overall 'looser' way of life.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "generation", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Three teachers are going to ____ at the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The candidate must command clear written and ____ communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is not a ____ in the notion of economic development as much as it is a problem with the fiscal structure of Alaska.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The links between ____ price declines and food prices are not easy to discern.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The chairman of the meeting forgot to ____ the guest speaker.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Student Activities Committee presented a project designed to ____ awareness of the ongoing crisis in the Sudan.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "raise", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While mastery of both written and spoken English is considered to be an ____ attribute, students with documented hearing, speech and other disabilities will be reasonably accommodated in accordance with law.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "differentiate", "Opt_2": "insist", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_2_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We should seriously ____ the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally feasible option.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Cats and young children are similar: they both like to ____ new places.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "succeed", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's sphere is, also advises man on woman's ____ and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "potential", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors should give ____ advice and treatment to all patients, whether rich or poor.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Rather than worrying about anthrax, this is the time of year to make sure that those at high ____ for the flu receive their vaccinations.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "exceed", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to be more than or better than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "All around the school are small white boxes which can ____ smoke and set off the fire alarm.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "With the passing of time the details of specific events ____ as they taken from the forefront of our mind and placed into the mainstream of our memory.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government met this morning to ____ how to help people who have been hit by the flood crisis.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "debate", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We will facilitate ____ and development in our district communities by serving as a key educational resource.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These findings suggest that something in the brain's pain-processing and pain-killing systems may ____ by race and ethnicity.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I would also ____ that you contact your physician for further information.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "shrink", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "forego", "Opt_4": "determine", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We hoped to find ____ data on why certain people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Are you ____ of the fact that you may fail the course?", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A headache may seem like a ____ problem, but it could be the sign of something more serious.", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Before having a major surgical ____ patients must always consent.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "procedure", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school's facilities have been improved ____ with the addition of a second library and media centre.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was given to the grandmother by her grandfather in 1852, when the ____ was a member of the California assembly.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the funding is from personal or family funds, you will need to obtain a ____ bank statement showing that you have enough funds to cover expenses.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "vast", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Employees must have worked for the State for at least five years, and have a satisfactory ____ of sick leave usage and work performance.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "record", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "And finally, these estimates depend to some ____ on those proven numbers and, as we've already seen, those numbers are not very reliable.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "extent", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "size, amount", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The siting and design are a typical ____ of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "crucial", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "extremely important", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I was unable to ____ the reason for Angelica's sudden departure at the beginning of the second trimester.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "discover", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Those who will be attending the event should try to make it to the Speedway early to ____ the rush hour traffic.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Using computer modeling, he was able to deduce the ____ between the strength of a stellar wind and the age of a star.", "Opt_1": "relationship", "Opt_2": "atmosphere", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_2_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main objective of this ESL course is to improve students' ____ in academic writing.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the common ____ of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "outcome", "Opt_2": "factor", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to discern how grammar and usage errors can ____ with meaning.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A student seeking a career in this field of study will have ____ opportunities to develop personal and professional skills.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "particular", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "specific"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you choose not to participate or to ____ from the study at any time, there will be no penalty.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company plans to ____ training videos on its intranet website.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The university follows a ____ policy of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "strict", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "hard, not changeable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 issue of Nature, the investigators report that female mice ____ the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A close study of this ____ will reward any reader.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "To ____ eligible for financial aid, recipients are required to show satisfactory progress toward a degree according to the guidelines listed below.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "regard", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "One particular group of bacteria, the \"blue-green algae,\" have left a fossil ____ that extends far back into the Precambrian Era.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "province", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All the ESL student's teachers can ____ influence the speed at which he or she learns English.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Women often earn less money that men doing the same job. This ____ must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What is the correct ____ sequence on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "key", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is the single most important ____ a district judge can perform in the administration of his duties.", "Opt_1": "degree", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your reading is improving fast, but you should not ____ your writing. It is through writing that you show your teachers what you know or have understood.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Should the government ____ more in solar energy or nuclear energy? It's a difficult choice.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "halt", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A dangerous ____ took place on the border between Israel and Egypt.", "Opt_1": "fault", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Microsoft has promised that the forthcoming operating system will be more ____ than ever before.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A rich parent has donated money to the school to ____ the building of a new sports block.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My friend is very ____ ; if she says she will do something she never forgets it.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to ____ to better themselves with the opportunity afforded them.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "strive", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "reduce", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to make smaller or shorter"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She was unable to ____ her ability and experience to this new problem.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "English has simple grammar but ____ spelling rules, whereas in German the opposite is true.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is no ____ of sentimentality in Weil's notion of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "trace", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Use positive words and phrases; don't ____ the energy of the interview by focusing on the negative.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "drain", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "drain", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Is there anything wrong with him? His behaviour has been very ____ recently.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ his plans for an industrial area, which he purchased from the Israel Land Administration.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A group of artists who were working and teaching in the Boston area had a bold idea: to create a new kind of school for professional education in the ____ arts.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "visual", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ is such that not only is the Muslim community conflicted with the outside pressures to conform, but it is conflicted within itself.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "situation", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The director was not prepared to even listen to ideas ____ to his own.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "display", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "contrary", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The chances of young people becoming criminal ____ if they live in poor housing with drug-addicted parents.", "Opt_1": "multiply", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The future energy system will need to ____ the unacceptable risk that the present system places on the environment.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "eliminate", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School needs to ____ its curriculum with that of German state schools.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "adjust", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people think it was no ____ that there was a terror alarm two days before the election.", "Opt_1": "reply", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "coincidence", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "an answer", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "an uncommon happening of two things"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the formula for weight ____ is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The police are trying to ____ the men seen on camera breaking the bus shelter.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She chose to reject the ____ that there is an increased risk of having a second child with the same disorder.", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I ____ my teacher for not preparing us properly for the test.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The new law will ____ unmarried mothers.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must differentiate ____ for students.", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The self-hatred that this ____ inflicted led the children to attempt to wash their skin white with scouring powder.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "consequence", "Answer": "prejudice", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There was a ____ demonstration on the streets of London to protest the government's plans to go to war in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Mechanisms by which comfrey can ruin the liver are unclear, but the ____ injury appears to be destruction of small veins, leading to cirrhosis.", "Opt_1": "main", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Try to communicate that the process is more important than the answer so that the student learns that it is OK to not have an ____ solution.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most famous footballers and film stars need an ____ to take care of their contracts.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She claimed, furthermore, that the ____ did not acknowledge the positive developments in the industry since the turn of the century.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Most of the families at our international school are here for a ____ of 2-3 years The ____ of the Earth's orbit around the sun is 365 days.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "duration", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is extremely important to ____ the installation with all parties involved.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "coordinate", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While I don't present this as absolutely the ____ method that everyone should use, it is important that a standardized technique be adopted.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you discover that you have the wrong textbook, you must contact the source from which you purchased the book and make arrangements to ____ the book.", "Opt_1": "solve", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "depend", "Opt_4": "imply", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to give to understand"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in ____ but nevertheless wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some politicians fear that too much immigration will ____ in fewer jobs for the people born in the country.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Both of these programs can be amended as needed to ____ a particular area of vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to ____ its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Significant progress has been toward reaching this ____ through the broad workforce planning effort as well as specific unit managerial decisions.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "sequence", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "repeat", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "comprise", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to do or say again", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "faint", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "not strong"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We explain that at each movement in the dance there are endless opportunities to ____ new ideas.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "fluctuate", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to vary; to rise and fall"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We must reverse the ____ of a growing incidence of campus hate crimes.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "How do we approach the essential and ____ problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "perpetual", "Answer": "perpetual", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school faces a real ____ in educating students from poor backgrounds.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to provoke much discussion ____ teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You can buy each ____ on the school supplies list from the bookstore.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "context", "Answer": "item", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "the place or situation in which something is found"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic ____ was rapid and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "growth", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Police investigating the scene of the crime have taken away an ____ that they have not yet been able to identify.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "object", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "thing", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is a highly ____ view of the symbolic nature of physical reality.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "credible", "Answer": "subjective", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "believable"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people ____ pictures to the emails they send.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of ____ to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The conclusion did not ____ the truth of the situation even though the student ____ed some of the data that he collected.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The manager used the ____ of the opening of the new factory block to make a speech about future developments.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I can ____ on a moderate income. I don't need lots of money.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "survive", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to not die", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We wish to employ women who want to invent, create, and ____ the next generation of computers, and computing methodology.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "passage", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of written or spoken text"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We engage outside counsel to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "But when planned and deliberate policy forces the price of oil down without good ____ reasons, then that means another war against Iraq.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "satisfactory", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I MUST see the headmaster at once! It's ____ !", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "proper", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You need to know a little more about the ____ before you criticize the government's decision.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The more information a sentence carries, the more it needs an evident ____ that the reader can follow.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "equipment", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some people have claimed that the ____ reason for the invasion of Iraq was to gain control of the oil fields.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "reasonable", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "sole", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "attend", "Opt_4": "speculate", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_4_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you do not have a particular title in mind, but wish to ____ that the library purchase more material on a specific subject, please enter your name.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "However, his proposal contains a ____ that is important to recognize and understand.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "debt", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "something owed to another person (often money)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "exact", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a ____ corner of Antarctica can disrupt an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to ____ the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and retain employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The two departments have failed to ____ and coordinate their efforts in implementing the laws and regulations on the use of wetland areas.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The programme will include several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will ____ in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the programme.", "Opt_1": "unite", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "indicate", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If faculty ____ that a mental health problem may be the cause of a student's violation of the Student Code of Conduct, they should contact the Dean of Students immediately.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an optional tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the ____ of restoration.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "process", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a series of steps"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Nevertheless, even within the period 1550-1850 there was a great ____ of temperature variation both in time and space.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are accepted you will need to arrange to have an official copy of your scores sent to the Program ____ below.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My biggest ____ about the book is that Gruchy did not insert his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The faculty member cannot refuse a reasonable request for extension of the project ____ date.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I am surprised at the directors' ____ inability to understand how the workers are feeling.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ordinary people who are caught up in ____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "appropriate", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ of the project will include all processes, people, organizational structures, systems and facilities currently in place.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A ____ problem is that many companies will only employ workers with experience, but how do young people gain that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production process may be reduced if a sufficiently large ____ is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Excellent writing with just one or two ____ mistakes!", "Opt_1": "trivial", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "not important", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For many persons these are not ____ concerns but profound and deep beliefs.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "probable", "Opt_4": "trivial", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_4_def": "not important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In this report you must write a comparison of FIS and your ____ school.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ and often unclear structure of the organizational responsibilities enabled energetic managers to network.", "Opt_1": "loose", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "common", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "loose", "Opt_1_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Lack of sufficient ____ often prohibits sound management activities that are necessary to the company's long-term health and stability.", "Opt_1": "implication", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government is planning to set up an ____ to document climate change.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "sphere", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and occasionally requires travel away from the normal ____ station.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "duty", "Opt_4": "license", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_4_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's new proposals are too vague. They need to be ____ about what they expect people to do.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I'm sorry but the school has no ability to educate children with ____ learning problems.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "When the moisture con____s, heat is released into the air, making it warmer and less ____ than its surroundings.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To accurately determine mass balance, stakes were placed in the ____ clean ice areas of the glacier.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "voluntary", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "adjacent", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "next to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are a few steps you can take to further ____ that construction activities do not damage the environment.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The main ____ of the committee is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "ambitious", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Since the human body is not an object that can be disposed of at will, the results of ____ should be made available to the whole scientific community.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she plagiarized her research essay.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "delay", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "lateness"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was an extremely conservative institution, and did not ____ its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "restrict", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Look at the ____ of your book. Did your dog try to eat it?", "Opt_1": "condition", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "state", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Even very low temperatures do not ____ the strength of this material.", "Opt_1": "affect", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors were unable to ____ the man who was pulled out of the icy river.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "justify", "Opt_4": "claim", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to state to be true"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Well done. The result of all your ____ is an fine grade in your ESL test.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "source", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "where something begins, where you can find something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Great Britain, Canada, and the United States do not intend to reveal the secret until ____ have been found to control the bomb.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You will need to provide a ____ of recent writing so that your English level can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "How do we approach the ____ and perpetual problem of dealing with our own waste?", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "ambitious", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students ____ feedback from the teacher on their performance on the interpretative task before they start on the next one.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "recover", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to get back", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is the president who will need to encourage the strategic thinking and action necessary to attract and ____ employees of quality.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will persist in the immediate future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of education ____ strategies.", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "advance", "Answer": "reform", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to go or move forward; to get better"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your password should ____ only letters or numbers.", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is ____ a reason why the majority of past safety research has focused on organization and actions.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "dynamic", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His problems are largely ____ to poor concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Doctors often fail in their attempt to persuade patients to stop smoking. The ____ is too addictive.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "administration", "Opt_3": "grant", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_3_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The rising price of oil could ____ in a global economic disaster.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I hope to ____ a good grade in my grammar test.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "gain", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Beethoven was not an ideal parent and ____ friction developed between the two, contributing to his son's attempted suicide in 1826.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Asia is our closest ____ and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and exchange culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "facilities", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In an ____ group, each person can exert sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This is a very brief and inadequate ____ of a few of the leading points in a very large investigation with which I am occupied.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The construction of new facilities is an ____ for any university to make a clear statement about its environmental concern.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "opportunity", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The prime minister has said that he has no plan to resign over the ____ in Iraq.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The researchers did not ____ people with known chronic disease from their study.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "exclude", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ will move to a 42-volt electrical system within this decade.", "Opt_1": "journey", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Individuals with communication disorders have ____ difficulty making themselves clearly understood.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "identical", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "exactly the same"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Iron is a major ____ of hemoglobin that carries oxygen to all parts of the body.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental ____ are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "justice", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ that we consider our own faults before we are too loud about the faults of others.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will ____ and whether the United States should promote its ____ has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government wants to ____ young mothers in poor areas to attend parenting classes.", "Opt_1": "share", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A popular kind of literature these days is about the lives of ____ people who are caught up in extra____ events such as war or terrorism.", "Opt_1": "ordinary", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs elementary competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Advertising often tries to promote the idea that the customer deserves to buy the product because they are ____ it!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "ESL teachers often ask their students to ____ words in class.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "define", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ its success in fighting unemployment.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The OCC provides ____ and legal advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of rational choices that a criminal would make in the decision to ____ a crime.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Above all, a teacher must be ____ when dealing with requests for grade changes and other related matters.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "firm", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The whole new ____ of purchasing drugs \"on line\" is another area where care and common sense are essential.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Injuries occur when there is a certain blow or pressure against the head, damaging the ____ of the brain.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "debate", "Opt_4": "custom", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_4_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is difficult to change an unhealthy eating ____ that has developed from a very early age.", "Opt_1": "deed", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "term", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "an action", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "a word or expression"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "phenomenon", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Successful people ____ to have four underlying beliefs: I choose to succeed. I can succeed. I will succeed. I have succeeded.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Teachers do not always immediately ____ bad behaviour in class. Sometimes it is better to have a quiet talk with the student at the end of the lesson.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This document will explain some of the problems that could exist because the computer is unable to ____ updates for Windows Vista.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "install", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "motivate", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On your first day in a new school it is difficult to ____ all the information that you are given.", "Opt_1": "impose", "Opt_2": "evaluate", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "reinforce", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to make something stronger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She has not been making much ____ in the last few weeks. I think the counselor should talk to her and find out if anything is wrong.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "effort", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Wonderwise is a ____ of educational packages introducing you to women who have made science their career.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "interval", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "a period of time", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Though all of them are presented in English, there is a significant ____ in clarity between the various reports.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "context", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no place for those who have failed to ____ to better themselves with the opportunity afforded them.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "strive", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to work or try hard"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school has installed emergency buttons in each classroom as a precaution ____ intruders.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "indirectly", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social ____ as a dumping ground for their spare cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "finance", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "crisis", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In his view, the Empire was less a place where England exerted ____ than where it lost command of its own identity.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "utilize", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "appear", "Answer": "control", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to come, be seen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices gradually decreased until ____ zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "virtually", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She was in conflict with her parents at home and this was having a negative ____ on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the government's decision to invade Iraq.", "Opt_1": "form", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no point in getting angry with security ____ at airports. They have no choice but to follow orders.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "trait", "Opt_3": "staff", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_3_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The service ____ of the UK economy is much more successful than the manufacturing ____.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "sector", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "part; area"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Antarctica is a very ____ environment. Many explorers have lost their lives there.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "hostile", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "retain", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "underlie", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Director develops and oversees an ____ program of professional development and leadership training for history and social science teachers.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "willing", "Opt_4": "abstract", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_4_def": "not specific or concrete"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Collecting information with no ____ plan or purpose and then hoping to transform it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "particular", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some countries, such as Switzerland, remained ____ in the last world war.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "straightforward", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You have had ____ chances to improve your behaviour. Now it's too late.", "Opt_1": "key", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To include an ____ on your website, you will need to insert the ____ into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "vary", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "to change or be different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Eat less, exercise more: the ____ for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Mike is feeling very unwell. Can you please ____ him to the nurse?", "Opt_1": "offer", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We should avoid the ____ of assuming that we will ever be able to comprehend the causes of his behaviour.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the ____ is suitable for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "latter", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "latter", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Some people advocate government elections every four years ____ of every five as at present.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For example, in many manufacturing processes several nominally rigid bodies undergo multiple, concurrent, ____ frictional contacts.", "Opt_1": "spare", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "legal", "Opt_4": "dynamic", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "not needed", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_4_def": "changing; growing; energetic"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Human rights activist John Prendergast, who will present the lecture \"Stopping Genocide\", is ____ the notable speakers coming to campus.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These three young women have exhibited the kind of inner strength, commitment to friendship, patience and self-control that one ____ sees.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "hardly", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "not very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A ____ method of learning vocabulary is to write words and their translations in a small notebook.", "Opt_1": "certain", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "classic", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "sure", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We will not prevail unless some of you not only believe in the Constitution, but are willing to ____ in public service.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "subsidize", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to support financially"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "suppose", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Humans have a strong ____ to make inferences and hold causal beliefs, even though it is not rational.", "Opt_1": "attribute", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is going to ____ a law that will prohibit smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "introduce", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The following information has been prepared to serve as a ____ to assist you in establishing criteria for a successful teaching practice.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Mathews touches on an ____ that has puzzled students of American regional religious history.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The students began to ____ when their teacher told them they would have a test on the last day before Christmas.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The document was intended to ____ everything from minerals, through the kingdom of plants, to the highest animals.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "comprise", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sometimes it becomes more important to modify tried-and-tested methods and habits rather than ____ more resources.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These results are interesting, though not ____ to interpret.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The quality of your ideas and organization is much more important than the ____ of words you write.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Contrary to what you've been told by Courtney Love and the manipulated media reports, Kurt Cobain had no ____ for suicide.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will ____ the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will ____ the economic burden on society.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "fear", "Opt_4": "admit", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to enter"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Individuals should report the incident to a faculty or ____ member at the university with whom they are comfortable.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "technique", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Specifically, you ____ that you were not provided with academic adjustments and auxiliary aids, and were not provided access to other services and programs at the College.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "express", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She came to school yesterday ____ feeling very unwell.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "What is the next letter in the ____ O, T, F, S, N, E, _?", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "affair", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the ____ against global warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "aim", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "goal or intention"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "incorporate", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to include"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She ____ has to start attending school regularly. That will solve all her problems.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "merely", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The study included a ____ of the main concepts of the authors' model on connecting children with nature and community.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The first effort to produce a revised ____ started during the mid-1980s and failed to culminate in a new agreement.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "affair", "Answer": "policy", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "an event or series of events"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most countries that went to war in Iraq now ____ their decision.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "recognize", "Answer": "regret", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "overlap", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to have in common; to cover part of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "My parents ____ a lot of money from their investments in internet companies.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "derive", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the next 50 years the world's weather could ____ significantly if the polar ice continues to melt.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "alter", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Two thousand years from now, an archaeologist will find little ____ of the millions of web pages that have been updated in the last hour.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The bulk of the ____ money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "How people ____ to music is subjective. What sounds good to one person may sound terrible to another.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "enter", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or ____ admission.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "deny", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Check the ____ below for specific dates and starting times.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, thus is unable to ____ insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "measure", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Tobacco smoke was a ____ of life up through the 1970s.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "victory", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "win", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In most companies you have to have a high ____ before you are entitled to a company car.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}]]